directoryfever.com 2010-06-06

# DirectoryFever.com - SEO Optimized Free Link Directory - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**Collection of Information  
**We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to our mailing list.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
**The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors.  Personal information is not collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
